# Chris Cleveland



#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER IN ST. LOUIS, MO**

PHONE 618-806-0272 | EMAIL cwc0202@gmail.com

GITHUB https://github.com/cwc0202 | LINKEDIN https://www.linkedin.com/in/chris-cleveland-995b59102/

I want to solve problems by learning, doing good, and raising the floor for everyone. Years of experience in nursing and retail logistics combine to give me a unique perspective that I can apply to problems. As a lifetime student and helper, I want to take my skills and find places where I can make a difference.

LANGUAGES		FRAMEWORKS	DATABASES	TOOLS
<ul> <li>JavaScript</li> </ul>	• Java	• AngularJS	• MySQL	• Hibernate
<ul> <li>Typescript</li> </ul>	• HTML5/CSS3	•Thymeleaf		• Axios

### **PROJECT EXPERIENCE**

Recipe HIve — Recipe database app for the home chef

- Learn team based Agile software development through hands-on experience.
- Collaborated to create back end Models in an MVC architecture.
- Collaborated to create a RESTful API

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Field Nurse/Care Coordinator, ARJ/PromptCare Infusions, St. Louis, Jan 2023 - Present

Staff Nurse, SSM Health Cardinal Glennon Children's Hospital, St. Louis MO, Aug 2019 - Jan 2023

- Utilize leadership skills by coordinating and collaborating with the patient, family, significant other(s), communities, and members of the inter-professional team in assessing needs, setting goals, planning interventions, providing care, and evaluating outcomes.
- Apply the existing body of evidence-based practice and scientific knowledge in health care to nursing practice, ensuring that nursing care is delivered based on patient's age-specific and clinical needs

Retail Planner, Weekends Only Furniture and Mattress, St. Louis, MO, Sept 2010 - Aug 2019

- Ensure attainment of company sales objectives and inventory budgets through forecast planning, logistic and order management.
- Analyze categories for turn, GMROI and recommend actions to improve to Merchandise Manager.

#### **EDUCATION**

**LaunchCode,** LC101 Programming Course — 2023 **Southwestern Illinois College,** A.S. Nursing — 2019

**Southwestern Illinois College,** A.S. — 2012